<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Riya Sharma&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Riya Sharma&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Rendering</title>
      <link>/post/post-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/post-1/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STEPLANT.(Indoor Gardening)</title>
      <link>/blogs/blog-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/blog-1/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/project1.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;steplamt&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;research&#34;&gt;RESEARCH&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The research mainly included surveys, questionnaire, brainstorming without any direction, help and interviews.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;/images/brainstorming.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;BRAINSTORMING&#34; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The brainstorming session was the first thought we had related to the topic. It was a tool
for generating as much as solutions or ideas as possible for the topic. Later we &lt;em&gt;defined the
problem , layed out the context and definitions , included the right people , set the
agenda and then started holding the sessions&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;SECONDARY RESEARCH.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;gist of problems&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;changes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;improvement factors&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;classification of planters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;design statements&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;The topic was now finalized as PLANTERS&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The detailed research began and we now found our PROBLEM AREAS, which were:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;● REPOTTING : After a certain stage, a plant starts growing to an extent where
the normal size planter cannot hold its strength and so depending on each
plant, the repotting session happens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;● WATERING SYSTEM : People generally do not use a watering can to water
their plants ; also each plant acquires a limited amount of water. The most
preferred technique is spray bottle, sprinkling water, water bottles or a pipe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;● CLIMATE CHANGES : Climate changes depend on the area, city, country. But
the required protection methods are not taken. When in Summers , the plant
requires some shadow which is totally neglected. Other seasons face the
problems related to the atmosphere there.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;● CLEANLINESS : The major issue faced in indoor gardening system is the
cleanliness issue as most of the planters leave the water stains on the tiles.
Also terracotta planter is a big task to handle but is eventually best for the
plant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;● DRAINAGE SYSTEM : The indoor balconies usually don’t have a proper
drainage system, they mostly call people to clean and maintain it. Also least
attention is paid to this system.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;● SPACE : Because the balconies have a limited amount of space, the planters
are very compact and do not have enough space for breathing. Also the
person does not have enough space to walk in and take care of the plant.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;● PLANTERS USED : There are various types of planters used such as
terracotta,plastic, glazed ceramic, etc. Each of it’s pros and cons. Depends
totally on the user on what planter he prefers.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>